Rill Flow is a high-performance and scalable
distribution process programming service
that was initially designed to address the complexity of
the processes under the microblog video business scenario
and the performance problems
associated with the implementation of large traffic tasks
so that ease of usage,
high and low latency is a core feature of Rill Flow.
At present, Rill Flow has been widely used in Weibo
with a daily processing volume of tens of millions
supporting the core processes of
Weibo multiple businesses such as business orchestration,
associated with the implementation of large traffic tasks